<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyNotesApp</string>
    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Enigmatic Glass Sculpture</item>
        <item>Quantum Espresso Machine</item>
        <item>Celestial Garden Gnomes</item>
        <item>Harmonic Wind Chimes</item>
        <item>Time-Traveling Umbrella</item>
        <item>Luminous Kinetic Sand</item>
        <item>Astral Scented Candles</item>
        <item>Bionic Bonsai Tree</item>
        <item>Galactic Snack Dispenser</item>
        <item>Holographic Puzzle Globe</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item> A mesmerizing piece of art crafted from translucent glass, this sculpture captures and reflects light in unpredictable patterns, leaving observers in awe of its mysterious beauty.</item>
        <item>A cutting-edge coffee maker that uses quantum principles to brew the perfect cup. Its innovative technology promises a flavor experience that transcends the ordinary, transporting coffee enthusiasts to a new dimension of taste.</item>
        <item>Whimsical garden gnomes adorned with tiny spacesuits and rocket backpacks, these celestial guardians add a touch of interstellar charm to any outdoor space, bringing joy and wonder to passersby.</item>
        <item>More than just musical instruments, these wind chimes are meticulously tuned to produce harmonious tones that resonate with the surrounding environment, creating a soothing and melodic atmosphere.</item>
        <item>A seemingly ordinary umbrella with a twist – it allows its user to travel through time. With each opening, the umbrella transports its holder to a different era, making rainy days an unexpected adventure through history.</item>
        <item>A mesmerizing variation of kinetic sand that glows in the dark. Moldable and fluid, this sand not only provides a satisfying tactile experience but also emits a soft, ethereal glow when the lights are turned off.</item>
        <item>Candles infused with the essence of distant galaxies and cosmic wonders. Each fragrance tells a celestial story, invoking a sense of wonder and tranquility as the scents transport you to the far reaches of the universe.</item>
        <item>A fusion of nature and technology, this bonsai tree is equipped with tiny sensors and actuators that allow it to respond to the environment. It adapts its shape and movements, creating a dynamic and ever-changing piece of living art.</item>
        <item>A futuristic snack dispenser that offers an array of extraterrestrial treats. From meteorite-shaped chocolates to alien-inspired gummies, this dispenser turns snack time into a cosmic experience.</item>
        <item>A mind-bending puzzle in the form of a globe that challenges enthusiasts to piece together holographic images of famous landmarks and landscapes. Assembled, it becomes a stunning 3D representation of our diverse and beautiful planet.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>